{
    "subject": "resource/The_Killing_Fields_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/distributor",
    "object": "resource/Warner_Bros.",
    "human_readable": "The film 'The Killing Fields' was distributed by Warner Bros.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8840200901031494,
            "question": "Who distributed the film 'The Killing Fields'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8587468862533569,
            "question": "What other films were released by Warner Bros. around the same time as 'The Killing Fields'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7640981078147888,
            "question": "What is the name of the film distributed by Warner Bros.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7211918830871582,
            "question": "Name a film distributed by Warner Bros."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.547467052936554,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in films distributed by Warner Bros.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4934866726398468,
            "question": "Is 'The Killing Fields' a documentary or a fictional film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3464702367782593,
            "question": "When was 'The Killing Fields' likely released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.325308233499527,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'The Killing Fields' likely to belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.264754056930542,
            "question": "What kind of company is Warner Bros.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1988784521818161,
            "question": "Do you know any actors who starred in 'The Killing Fields'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The film 'The Killing Fields' was distributed by Warner Bros.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7003_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of company is Warner Bros.?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7003_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film 'The Killing Fields' likely to belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7003_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was 'The Killing Fields' likely released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7003_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7003_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7003_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7003_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7003_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7003_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7003_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7003_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7003_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7003_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7003_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis answer is derived from the document information stating, \"The Killing Fields (film) is distributed by Warner Bros., and Columbia-EMI-Warner.\" This confirms that Warner Bros. was indeed involved in distributing the film 'The Killing Fields.'"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}